it's in draft bro it's crazy
it's been more than a month since my brother has been me around
return my car
and out of nowhere I find out that the car is here in Osasco
it's pulling no hand
who is Caio mano
hi bro I just came to get the car not needing to work
I came come in there then
hold that dog there bro it's good
that this guy or there or there
dog there o brother now it's fixed to the head
it's not on i cheat with social network
mano then guys call bro
this is the guy who did this on my Chevette ó
this bro oh
brother just want the car just and get out brother
I'm fine then
return the fag car comes
here we will see if you will recognize
beauty customized the car
entire
bro changed the banks creating my brand logo
skate wheel there or Charlie Brown
you notice here what he did bro
pink details here too
upholstery all brown there's the closed glass
braked cut ignition
connect on your cell phone
help me with this one how do i do it
caraca has blue bro
lie man there it increases on the cell phone
caraca hand
love was out to get me
people are believing
that it was but it's actually pure
Mark's juice
strong hand dear
it got more than that mark the wheel
he also broke
guy he
gave a brown detail
on the wheel that got the shape of the brownie right
on the skate wheel
is
that bro if you want
bring your car here in the atelier 3 b s
talk to Tarsus
that he will customize his car and leave
the way you want it's on that's it
brings the idea that we make happen
Charlie Brown we are with our brother
we are together follows we are worth
it got crazy let's go for a ride in that car then bro
take a roll in this car here now uncle tô boa
now i'm managing to relax it's on
I'm going to ask the guys to take off their tennis to get in that car
is on
One more time
i'm in love
Come on
i believe i believe i believe i believe